<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
				<!-- RSS generated by Naval Systems Inc. (NSI) on {ts '2012-09-04 14:33:34'} -->
		 		<rss version="2.0">
			    <channel>
			       <title>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</title>
			       <link></link>
			       <description>All NSI News Items</description>
			       <language>en-us</language>
			       <copyright>Copyright 2009 Naval System, Inc. (NSI)</copyright>
			       <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 14:33:34 EST</lastBuildDate>
			       <image>
			            <title>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</title>
			            <url>/images/logo.gif</url>
			            <link></link>
			       </image>
			
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded subcontract for Strategic Operations Support</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>Under this contract, NSI supported environmental scan for the Naval Air Warfare Center Aircraft Division (NAWCAD) to increase NAWCAD leadership environmental strategic awareness in support of the NAWCAD Assistant Commander for Strategic Operations. NSI&amp;rsquo;s environmental scan assessed the Political, Economic, Social, Technological and Operational influences NAWCAD operations and strategies, enabling a more proactive and strategic approach to business operations in support of the Warfighter. The assessment includes an analysis of the implications of NAWCAD operations and an assessment of the patterns this task supports as well as working meetings to gain an understanding of these environmental conditions for incorporation into NAWCAD strategic plans and strategies.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/24</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Seaport Prime Contract for FMS Support for PMA 209</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI&amp;nbsp;will provide a full range of engineering, financial, logistics, and program management support services needed for successful International Fleet mission executions.&amp;nbsp; Under this task order, NSI will support a full range of Foreign Military Sales (FMS) cases and programs managed by the FMS IPT.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/25</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>4th Annual Golf Tournament Another Success!</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>On June 7th 2012, NSI and STAR 98.3 hosted our 4th annual Golf Tournament to benefit the Southern Maryland Food Bank. This year&amp;rsquo;s tournament, held at Wicomico Shores in Southern Maryland, hosted over 80 golfers and raised over $7,000 to benefit the Southern Maryland Food Bank! Pictures from our golf tournament can be found by clicking on the golf ball icon located on NSI&amp;rsquo;s homepage. Our yearly tournament has raised over $25,000 all donated to the Southern Maryland Food Bank (SMFB) to help local families in need. To contact the food bank, call (301) 274-0695 or visit their website at http://www.smfb.somd.com&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/28</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded contract to provide Program Management Services to the AIR 1.4 Policy and Training Division and the SH-2G Aircraft programs.</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>On June 25, 2012, NSI was awarded a new Seaport-e delivery order (M806) to support the AIR 1.4 Policy and Training Division and the SH-2G Aircraft programs. In support of this effort, NSI will provide a full range of general program administration and management support services. Additionally, NSI will provide engineering, management and technical support services in the acquisition, life cycle management and upgrades of the SH-2G (E) weapon systems, tactical reference manuals and FMS training. NSI is teamed with General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) on this new effort.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/29</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded contract to provide Program Office Support to the PMA234 EA-6B Program Office</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>On June 29, 2012, NSI was awarded a new Seaport-e delivery order prime contract (M807) to provide Program Office Support to PMA234. NSI will provide system integration and logistics support, develop supportability, maintainability, availability, and cost analyses and develop and manage specific elements of configuration management. The EA-6B has been designated as the sole DOD escort Jamming aircraft and is a High Demand Low Density platform. PMA-234 has many on-going studies and modifications designed to ensure that the platform is safe and operationally effective throughout its expected service life ending in 2018. NSI is teamed with Engility Corporation and Atkinson Aeronautics and Technology.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/30</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded contract to provide PMA274 Presidential Helicopter Programs Logistics Support</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>On July 31, 2012 NSI was awarded a new Seaport-e delivery order (M809) to support PMA274 Logistics. In support of this effort, NSI will provide new acquisition and In-Service Integrated Product Support program management and logistics planning support services in the key areas of program/financial management, all integrated product support elements, configuration/modification management, inventory management, training support, acquisition logistics, sustainment logistics, and termination logistics support. NSI is teamed with National Technologies Associates (NTA) and Andromeda Systems Incorporated (ASI).&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/31</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded contract to provide PMA274 Presidential Helicopter Program Management Support.</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>On July 17, 2012 NSI was awarded a new Seaport-e delivery order (M808) to perform program management, acquisition management, technical, security and administrative support tasks to support the execution of PMA-274 acquisition programs. NSI is teamed with National Technologies Associates (NTA) and American Electronics, Inc. (Amelex).&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/32</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded contract to provide PMA231 Logistics Program Management Support.</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>On August 30, 2012, NSI was awarded a new Seaport-e delivery order (M810) to provide Logistics Program Management Support and Logistics Supportability Analyses for PMA 231 supported aircraft, Power and Propulsion System, and Support Equipment. PMA 231 aircraft include E-2C, E-2D, and C-2A. NSI is teamed with Wyle on this effort.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/33</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>Fall Food Drive a Success!</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI, partnered with STAR 98.3 and the ROCKET 97.7, held a very successful fall food drive on November 18, 2011.&amp;nbsp; Our efforts combined to raise close to $4000 which will be used by the Southern Maryland Food Bank to purchase over 32,000 pounds of food which will be distributed to local families in need.&amp;nbsp; The food drive also collected 3,392 pounds of food to help families this Thanksgiving!&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/26</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI awarded KC-130J Integrated Logistics Support</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI&amp;nbsp;has been awarded a subcontract to provide a full range of Integrated Logistics Support services to support the KC-130J.&amp;nbsp; Support services will include&amp;nbsp;Maintenance Planning and Analsyis, Quantitative Resource Analysis, Program Evaluation, Program Implementation, and Follow-on ILS Planning.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/27</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Subcontract to provide Program Management Services to assist in the execution of Naval Aviation Center for Rotorcraft Advancement (NACRA)</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>In support of this effort, NSI will provide program management services to assist in the execution of Naval Aviation Center for Rotorcraft Advancement (NACRA) goals in the areas of technology, acquisition, requirements, capability, infrastructure and documentation. In this capacity NSI will represent NACRA in the areas of rotorcraft programs, platforms, technology, requirements development and safety and survivability to support the Patuxent River rotary wing community and platform specific requirements within the program areas. To support this effort, NSI will work with representatives of NAWCAD team groups, OPNAV, HQMC, Naval Air Systems Command (NAVAIR) competencies, International Helicopter Society, Naval Safety Center, Defense Safety Oversight Committee, Industry and/or other military departments to develop common requirements, cooperative agreements, and standard policies for rotary wing technical solutions and common capabilities/missions such as crashworthiness, brown out, attack, Electronic Warfare and Aircraft Survivability Equipment.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>NSI will also serves as a NACRA representative for the Office of the Secretary of Defense Future Vertical Lift (FVL) initiative on behalf of the rotary wing community. We will provide expert advice, opinion, and assessment to assist FVL committee members in outlining a joint approach to the future development of a vertical lift aircraft for all military services.&amp;lt;br />
&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/23</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded PMA 209 Air Combat Electronics Cost Estimating & Analysis Task</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>Under this contract, NSI will develop cost analyses, cost models, cost analysis tools and provide general acquisition support for the Air Combat Electronics Program Office. Cost analysis support shall include cost and budget drills or excursions as directed by the Cost IPT Lead or Program Management Team. The analysis done during these drills will support program decision making and aid in planning through aircraft production. Acquisition support provided by NSI to IPT leads will provide the program office with direct insight into the processes and products the various IPTs are working towards and provide better understanding of the technical baseline being estimated.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/15</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded PMA 209 Air Combat Electronics Cost Estimating & Analysis Task to Provide MFOQA Support</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>Under this contract, NSI will develop cost analyses, cost models, cost analysis tools and provide general acquisition support for the Military Flight Operations Quality Assurance (MFOQA) program. Cost analysis support shall include cost and budget drills or excursions as directed by the Cost IPT Lead or Program Management Team. The analysis done during these drills will support program decision making and aid in planning through aircraft production. Acquisition support provided by NSI to IPT leads will provide the program office with direct insight into the processes and products the various IPTs are working towards and provide better understanding of the technical baseline being estimated. Other cost estimating / analyses and acquisition support for PMA 209 will be provided as required.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/16</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI is now a Service Disabled Veteran Owned Small Business</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI is very proud to announce our official certification as a Service Disabled Veteran-Owned Small Business (SDVOSB). The designation was obtained to provide an additional benefit to those clients who need to achieve SDVOSB contracting goals. NSI will continue to provide exceptional products and services under this new designation.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/17</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI part of L-3 Award of $187.4M contract for Systems Engineering and Technical Services Contract Issued by US Navy</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI is pleased to announce the award of a $187.4 million dollar L-3 prime contract cost plus fixed fee contract issued by the US Navy for Systems Engineering and Technical Support Services for the AIR 4.1 Competency at Naval Air Station (NAS) Patuxent River, MD. NSI is a proud team member of prime contractor L-3 Communications Command &amp;amp; Control Systems and Software (C2S2) Division and we congratulate them on this successful award! Under this contract, the L-3 team will provide a broad array of services including Systems Engineering, Systems/Subsystems Integration, Avionics/Software/Air Vehicle Technology Insertion, Survivability Engineering, Earned Value Management (EVM), Configuration Management, Reliability and Maintainability Engineering, Environmental Engineering, Program Performance Assessment Analysis/Planning, and Technology Transfer.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/18</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Follow-on to LOGCAP Effort</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI was awarded a follow-on effort to provide logistics acquisition and life cycle management support in support of in-theater efforts in IRAQ. NSI is in our third year of providing support under this contract. NSI will continue to successfully provide technical and audit services assistance related to property book management and accountability and technical and financial services assistance in support of in-theater efforts.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/19</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Press Release 6/13/2010 - LOCAL FIRM HELP FEED HUNGRY IN GOLF TOURNY</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI Press Release 6/13/2010&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>Lexington Park, MD &amp;ndash; Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI), headquartered in Lexington Park, Maryland, in conjunction with STAR 98.3 &amp;ldquo;T-Bone &amp;amp; Heather,&amp;rdquo; out of Mechanicsville, Maryland, raised over $7,700 for the Southern Maryland Food Bank through their 2nd Annual Charity Golf Tournament on June 10th at the Wicomico Shores Golf Course. Some 22 golf teams participated in the charity tournament, followed by prizes and a fund-raising auction. &amp;ldquo;A great time was had by all!&amp;rdquo; commented Diana Waldorf, NSI event organizer. The Southern Maryland Food Bank supports the communities of Calvert, Charles, and St Mary&amp;rsquo;s Counties and provides food to families in need. With the help of generous participants and sponsors, The tournament raised over $7,700 which will be used by the Food Bank to purchase over $60,000 pounds of food allowing the food bank to assist more than 3,000 families in need. To date, NSI and STAR 98.3 have raised over $15,000 to support the Southern Maryland Food Bank.&amp;lt;br />
&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/20</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Subcontract for Integrated Logistics Support for EA-6B ICAP III Trainers</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI, as a subcontractor to Chesapeake Technology International (CTI), was awarded a subcontract to generate processes and procedures necessary for development and maintenance of required LMI Data Products as well as supporting CTI in generating required LMI data products for the EA-6B ICAP III Trainers. Additionally, NSI will provide support in area of R&amp;amp;M activities and support in preparing for; coordinating and participating in the required ILS reviews as they pertain to current technology refresh and trainer upgrade projects. This effort is in support of CTI&amp;rsquo;s contract to provide a comprehensive ILS program for EA-6B ICAP III Block 4 and higher trainers located at the Marine Corps Air Station (MCAS) Cherry Point, North Carolina and Naval Air Station (NAS) Whidbey Island, Washington.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/21</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Option to Continue to Provide Support to PMA-234 Airborne Electronic Attack Program</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>Under a subcontract to JFTI, NSI was award an option that will allow NSI&amp;nbsp;to continue to provide Cost Estimating and Analysis Support for the Airborne Electronic Attack Programs supporting PMA 234.&amp;nbsp; Under this effort, NSI&amp;nbsp;provides cost analysis and estimating support to Airborne Electronics Attack (AEA) programs to include Next&amp;nbsp;Generation Jammer, Low Band Transmitter, ITALD-J, and Intrepid Tiger.&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/22</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Expands In-Theater Efforts</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI has been awarded a subcontract by SERCO NA to provide base closure assistance team support for the Logistics Civil Augmentation Program (LOGCAP) during the drawdown of United States Forces. NSI will facilitate and provide guidance and expertise to the LOGCAP Iraq Deputy Program Director (DPD) in order to successfully close or return coalition bases back to the Government of Iraq or land owners in accordance with the Multi-National Corps-Iraq (MNC-I) C7 base closure task list.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>&amp;lt;br />
&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/14</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Inaugrual Golf Tournament is a Hit!</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI, co-sponsored with STAR 98.3, held our 1st Annual Charity Golf Tournament on May 7, 2009 at the beautiful Cedar Point Golf Course located on NAVAIR, Patuxent River, MD.  Although the day started with some wet weather, all 100 participants were able to play thru and have a great time!  Proceeds for this year&amp;rsquo;s tournament went to support the &amp;lt;a target='_blank' href='http://www.smfb.somd.com'>Southern Maryland Food Bank&amp;lt;/a> (SMFB).  With the help of generous sponsors and donations, NSI and STAR 98.3 were able to raise $6,571 that will be used by the Southern Maryland Food Bank (SMFB) to purchase over 59,139 pounds of food that will help furnish local Maryland food banks so they can continue to support the over 10,000 families in need every month!  Additionally, we were able to collect 700 pounds of non-perishable food items that were also donated to SMFB.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>NSI would like to thank all the volunteers who supported this event and a special thank you to all the sponsors that played a key role in the tournament&amp;rsquo;s success.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>Planning for next year&amp;rsquo;s charity golf tournament is already in the works. We intend to hold our next tournament in June 2009.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>To view pictures of this event &amp;lt;a href='http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showGolf2009/'>click here&amp;lt;/a>.&amp;lt;/p>
&amp;lt;p>To hear Dan and Ed on the T-Bone and Heather, STAR 98.3 morning show, &amp;lt;a target='_blank' href='/nsiDraft/documents/golf2009.mp3'>click here&amp;lt;/a>&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/6</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Purchases Manufacturing, Repair, Overhaul and Logistics Division</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI announces the purchase of our new Manufacturing, Repair, Overhaul and Logistics (MRO&amp;amp;L) operation located in Jacksonville, FL. Our new division will specialize in the remanufacturing and rework of aerospace components and can provide a complete range of supply chain management functions and services.  With this purchase, NSI will becomes an FAA certified provider of Avionics, Instruments and Test Equipment repair and overhaul. NSI MRO&amp;amp;L provides the highest quality products and services at competitive prices, being registered to ISO9000:2000 and AS9100:2004 international quality standards. We are members of the National Society of Safety Professionals and the NE FL Safety Council.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/7</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>Presidential Helicopters Group Receives Oustanding Performance Recognition</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI&amp;rsquo;s Presidential Helicopters Program&amp;rsquo;s In-Service Logistics Team received a Letter of Appreciation from the Department of the Navy acknowledging their outstanding performance in support of mission objective.  Appreciation was provided to recognize their &amp;ldquo;selflessness, knowledge and eagerness to support all required efforts and their contributions to efficient and effective support to the VH-3D and VH-60N Presidential Helicopters program.&amp;rdquo;&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/8</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Option to Provide Performance Based Logistics Support to EA-6B Aicraft, NADEP Jacksonville, and PMA 234</title>
			         <description>NSI was award a follow-on contract to provide PBL and supply chain management services to prime contractor AAI in partnership with NADEP Jacksonville.  NSI will continue to provide logistics support services that will benefit the EA-6B aircraft, the operation and integration of the fleet, NADEP Jacksonville, and PMA 234.  Under this effort, NSI will continue to provide logistics element support and coordinate closely with NAVAIR/NADEP Jacksonville and NAVICP.</description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/9</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Expands In-Theater Cost Analysis and Property Support</title>
			         <description>NSI was awarded a follow-on effort to provide logistics acquisition and life cycle management support in support of in-theater efforts in IRAQ.  Over the past year, NSI has doubled the personnel originally proposed to support this effort.  NSI will continue to successfully provide technical and audit services assistance related to property book management and accountability and technical and financial services assistance in support of in-theater efforts.</description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/10</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded $1.5M Contract for Technology Transition Services to Programs Encompassing New Technology Development and Fleet In-Service Engineering Support</title>
			         <description>Under this contract, NSI will provide engineering support to Navy and Tri-Service air weapons systems including aircrafts of all types, unmanned air vehicles, missiles and or ordinance that is air, surface, or subsurface launched and the support equipment related to these systems.  The focus of this effort is Navy Small Business Innovative Research (SBIR) programs along with emerging technology programs related to unmanned systems and transition support for Counter-Improvised Explosive Device (CIED) technology.</description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/11</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI MRO&L Division Wins Agusta Westland Contract</title>
			         <description>Agusta Westland Inc. has contracted with NSI MRO&amp;L to repair/overhaul avionics instruments for Egyptian helicopters they are overhauling. NSI and Agusta Westland have just completed the Test and Evaluation phase and expect to enter into full production in early July 09. Agusta Westland plans to overhaul 24 Egyptian helicopters.</description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/12</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded PMA 231 Logistics and Technical Support Contract</title>
			         <description>Under this contract, NSI will continue to provide logistics and technical support for E-2C component recovery program for new productions for the E-2D aircraft.  Logistics support will also be provided to NAVICP, DCMA St. Augustine, AMARG and NG on SARDIP/Proposal Efforts.  Using Government owned Material (GOM) recovery program, NSI will continue to provide operations systems repair support for the E-2D aircraft.  Additionally, NSI will provide acquisition support of missing components for refurbishment of Foreign Military Sales (FMS) aircraft.</description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/13</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI to provide Logistics, Maintenance and Supply Support (LMSS) to the DoD</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>As a subcontractor to Booz, Allen and Hamilton, NSI will provide Logistics, Maintenance and Supply Support (LMSS) to DoD agencies including the Navy, Air Force and Marine Corps. This win will enable NSI to provide support to the Naval Air Systems Command (NAVAIR) Joint DoD Maintenance Resource Planning (MRP II) Program Office, PMA 203.  This contract supports the total life cycle systems management for business process services and solutions for logistics, maintenance, and supply functions and associated technologies.  These services/solutions include all life cycle management activities associated with the planning, implementation, execution, and retirement of business processes and systems solutions for DoD Logistics, Maintenance and Supply Support activities and associated business initiatives, as well as those activities required for moving to an enterprise-wide, life cycle alignment of resources and outputs to achieve top-down performance driven outcomes&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/3</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Opens Ridgecrest, CA Office</title>
			         <description>&amp;lt;p>NSI announces the opening of our newest office in Ridgecrest, CA. Our newest office will allow NSI personnel to provide a full range of subject matter expertise and technical services to the Naval Air Weapons Station, China Lake and surrounding community. This is NSI&amp;rsquo;s third office and follows the recent opening of our second office in Jacksonville, FL. Our Jacksonville, FL opened in the Fall of 2007.&amp;lt;/p></description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/4</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
			   <item>
			         <title>NSI Awarded Enterprise Architecture Contract (Patuxent River, MD)</title>
			         <description>NSI was awarded a contract to assist NAVAIR PMA 263 with the development of an Unmanned Aerial Systems (UAS) Family of Systems (FoS) enterprise architecture framework.  NSI will define an overarching FoS architecture that establishes a baseline to which the Naval NAS programs can migrate as required.   

NSI will also be responsible for developing a UAS FoS architecture strategy that guides the Common Systems Integration IPT and UAS program in implementing the FoS architecture.  Ultimately, the UAS FoS enterprise architecture will give leadership the tool to measure commonality, interoperability, and the degree to which they have an “open” architecture framework.</description>
			         <link>http://n-s-i.us/index.cfm/go/showNews/nid/5</link>
			         <author>Naval Systems, Inc. (NSI)</author>
			         <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
			   </item>
			   
